<?xml version="1.0"?>
<DataDrainConfig Version="1.0">
	<WordList>
		<Word ID="1" Name="Atoli">Atoli is a female Harvest Cleric and a member of the guild called Moon Tree. She is also an Epitaph User, and is the host for the Second Phase, Innis, the Mirage of Deceit.</Word>
		<Word ID="2" Name="Kuhn">Kuhn is a male Steam Gunner and the Epitaph User titled "The Propagation". He is the former Vice-Guildmaster of Kestrel, the founder of Canard, and is currently a member of Raven and the organization "G.U." He enjoys flirting with the female players of "The World R:2".</Word>
		<Word ID="3" Name="Pi">Pi is a system administrator of "The World R:2", and an Epitaph User, being able to summon the Avatar, Tarvos.</Word>
		<Word ID="4" Name="Silabus">Silabus is a member and former guild master of the guild Canard.</Word>
		<Word ID="5" Name="Gaspard">Gaspard is a character in .hack//G.U. and member of the guild Canard.</Word>
		<Word ID="6" Name="Piros">Piros, also Piros the 3rd, fills the role of a comic relief in the .hack//Games, which is most apparent in his encounters with Mia. He is the second player to join Kite and BlackRose.</Word>
		<Word ID="7" Name="Alkaid">Alkaid is a female Twin Blade and a former member of Icolo.</Word>
		<Word ID="8" Name="Saku">Saku is a female Shadow Warlock and an Epitaph User titled "The Machinator". Her brother, Bo, shares a character with her in "The World R:2". The character they share is named Sakubo. Saku and Bo are able to summon the Avatar, Gorre.</Word>
		<Word ID="9" Name="Endrance">Endrance is the Epitaph User titled "The Temptress". He is a Blade Brandier, and acknowledged as a powerful player, even by the strong players of The World R:2. He is also an AIDA-PC. Endrance is cold and has little interest in other players, and only shows emotion to the small cat on his shoulder. His Avatar is Macha.</Word>
		<Word ID="10" Name="Antares">Antares is a male Blade Brandier and the founder of Icolo, the arena emperors' guild. He considers Haseo his "apprentice."</Word>
		<Word ID="11" Name="Matsu">Matsu is a male Adept Rogue and Moon Tree's Seventh Unit leader. He used to be a famous PK known as the "Flame Sword Demon", before renouncing his ways and joining with Zelkova and Sakaki.</Word>
		<Word ID="12" Name="Yata">Yata is a male Macabre Dancer and a System Administrator dispatched to solve the problems plaguing "The World R:2". He is also the Epitaph User titled "The Prophet" and has the ability to call forth the Avatar, Fidchell.</Word>
		<Word ID="13" Name="Zelkova">Zelkova is a male Flick Reaper. He is the Guildmaster and also Moon Tree's First Unit leader . Moon Tree is a guild in "The World R:2" consisting of over 1000 pacifists and peace promoters. He is also the master of Net Slum. Whether the real world player behind Zelkova is also the same player behind legendary hacker, Helba, is unknown.</Word>
		<Word ID="14" Name="Shino">Shino is a female Harvest Cleric with the same character model as Atoli. She was the co-leader of the Twilight Brigade guild, which she ran along with Ovan. The character, Shino, was killed by the enigmatic PC, Tri-Edge, causing the real world player behind Shino's character to fall into a coma.</Word>
		<Word ID="15" Name="Bordeaux">Bordeaux is a female Blade Brandier and a Player Killer from the guild Kestrel.</Word>
		<Word ID="16" Name="Kaede">Kaede is Moon Tree's Third Unit leader and close friend of Zelkova.</Word>
		<Word ID="17" Name="Kite">Kite is the main character and the character you control in the first .hack game series.</Word>
		<Word ID="18" Name="Tabby">Tabby is a Tribal Grappler, a former member of the Twilight Brigade, and Guildmaster of the Paw Pad Squadron.</Word>
		<Word ID="19" Name="Natsume">Natsume is a young and naive Twin Blade that joins Kite's party when he gives her the Spiral Edge she was searching for. Normally a shy and socially awkward girl, she started playing "The World" because she wanted to change.</Word>
		<Word ID="20" Name="Haseo">Haseo is an Adept Rogue known as the "Terror of Death", and is the main character in .hack//Roots, .hack//G.U., and .hack//GU+. He is a PKKer who is in search of Tri-Edge, the legendary PK that previously attacked Haseo's friend, Shino and put her into a coma in the real world.</Word>
		<Word ID="21" Name="Salvador">Salvador Aihara, real name Carlos Aihara, is the main character of Online Jack, the OVA that plays during certain intervals in .hack//G.U.</Word>
		<Word ID="22" Name="Skeith">Skeith is the 1st Phase of the Cursed Wave and was referred to as "The Terror of Death".</Word>
		<Word ID="23" Name="Tarvos">Tarvos is the 7th Phase of the Cursed Wave and was referred to as "The Avenger".</Word>
		<Word ID="24" Name="Gabi">Gabi is a male Edge Punisher and the leader of the guild Kestrel.</Word>
		<Word ID="25" Name="Grein">Grein is a male Edge Punisher, a PK, and is one of Bordeaux's henchmen. He is a member of Kestrel. He says very little and, unlike Negimaru, is almost never seen without Bordeaux.</Word>
		<Word ID="26" Name="Negimaru">Negimaru is a male Twin Blade and one of Bordeaux's henchmen. Not just a mere underling, Negimaru is a bully who also has his own gang of PKs that consider him to be "very strong", but his fear of Haseo and Matsu has caused him to lose some face with them. He used to be independent, leading only that group, but Bordeaux challenged and defeated him, adding him to her roster of henchmen.</Word>
		<Word ID="27" Name="Sakaki">Sakaki is the Moon Tree's Second Unit leader. Atoli is one of the members of Sakaki's division and follows his commands.</Word>
		<Word ID="28" Name="Ovan">Ovan is a powerful Steam Gunner and the former leader of the Twilight Brigade. He is also an Epitaph User, being able to summon the Avatar, Corbenik.</Word>
		<Word ID="29" Name="Desktop">In graphical computing, a desktop environment offers a graphical user interface (GUI) to the computer. The name is derived from the desktop metaphor used by most of these interfaces, as opposed to the earlier, textual command line interfaces (CLI).</Word>
		<Word ID="30" Name="Forum">A forum is an application for holding discussions and posting user generated content.</Word>
		<Word ID="31" Name="Apkallu">Apkallu is an internet forum where users can exchange information or discuss topics of interest. Users of "The World" use its official BBS to give and receive gameplay help, discuss current events, or arrange a time and place to meet. Other forums unaffiliated with CC Corp exist as well, and usually have more lenient rules about content.</Word>
		<Word ID="32" Name="Grunty">Grunties are pig-like creatures that players of "The World" can raise in root towns as virtual pets. As a type of NPC, most Grunties can speak. Their backstory, appearance, and uses are dramatically different between the two different versions of "The World".</Word>
		<Word ID="33" Name="Honeysuckle">Honeysucke is a type of flower. Shino once presented Haseo with a pair of dual swords titled "Honeysuckle". The flower meaning of Honeysuckle is "devoted affection".</Word>
		<Word ID="34" Name="Canard">Canard is a newbie-friendly guild, dedicated to aiding newcomers to "The World R:2". The guild was founded by Kuhn when he left his position of Vice-Guildmaster of Kestrel. The fact that it is a newbie-related group makes it the target of Kestrel's PKers. Leadership passed to Silabus when Kuhn left to join Raven, and then finally to Haseo, because he is, according to Silabus, a "natural leader".</Word>
		<Word ID="35" Name="Raven">Raven is a mysterious guild led by Yata. The small guild is in fact just front for the secret group known as "G.U.".</Word>
		<Word ID="36" Name="Bracelet">The Twilight Bracelet is an item that gives the user the ability to Data Drain and Gate Hack. Its power may prevent the user's data from being altered, though this might also be simply a secondary effect of the install book used to acquire it.</Word>
		<Word ID="37" Name="Repth">Repth is the most basic and common healing spell in The World. It is also a Common card from the Contagion set of .hack//ENEMY.</Word>
		<Word ID="38" Name="Kestral">Kestrel is the largest guild in "The World R:2". The guild has over 5,000 members and contains many PKs because the guildmaster, Gabi, believes "that's just another part of 'The World'". Kuhn used to be Vice Guildmaster of Kestrel, before leaving and founding Canard.</Word>
		<Word ID="39" Name="Icolo">Icolo is a guild made up of the three Arena Emperors. It was originally founded by Antares as a place reserved for the most powerful Arena fighters. However Antares grew disillusioned when he discovered that the other Emperors valued their titles and the status it gave them more then their comrades or improving their skills. Leaving the Guild he gave his title of Guildmaster over to Taihaku, who still rules over the Guild to this day.</Word>
		<Word ID="40" Name="AIDA">AIDA stands for Artificially Intelligent Data Anomaly. It is a term used by CC Corp to refer to the "black spots" and the creatures that come out of them. Little is known about AIDA, but according to Yata, AIDA is primarily interested in humans. It is for this reason that it stays within "The World R:2", and does not spread out into the rest of the Internet. For this reason, Yata believes that "The World R:2" must remain open to its entire userbase, and not shut off to all but administrators.</Word>
		<Word ID="41" Name="Epitaph">In the .hack series, the word Epitaph refers to several things: Epitaph, the ninth episode of .hack//SIGN, the Epitaph of Twilight, an epic poem that "The World" was based on, and a name given to the Morganna Factors that exist inside of Epitaph Users.</Word>
		<Word ID="42" Name="Dungeon">Dungeons are areas players go to fight battles against Monsters, gain treasure, and get experience.</Word>
		<Word ID="43" Name="Net Slum">Net Slum is a place that exists in "The World", yet doesn't, as it isn't controlled by the System Administrators. It is a place where failed or unwanted data (such as vagrant AIs), and hackers gather.</Word>
		<Word ID="44" Name="Azure Orca">Azure Orca is one of the Three Azure Knights.</Word>
		<Word ID="45" Name="Tri-Edge">Tri-Edge is a legendary PK. It is said that players killed by Tri-Edge never log back in. These victims are known as "Lost Ones". He leaves a three-edged Sign at the location of his victims, and this is the source of his name.</Word>
		<Word ID="46" Name="Crimson VS">Crimson VS is an online card game for ALTIMIT Mine OS. It can be played using .hack//G.U.</Word>
		<Word ID="47" Name="Mac Anu">Mac Anu is the root town of the delta server Many @HOMEs are located here, and many Lost Grounds can be accessed through the chaos gate in this root town.</Word>
		<Word ID="48" Name="Breg Epona">The city of Breg Epona replaces Fort Ouph as the root town of sigma server in "The World R:2".</Word>
		<Word ID="49" Name="Moon Tree">Moon Tree is a guild of pacifists, promoting harmony and peace in "The World R:2". It is composed of around 1,000 members who are devoted to restoring "The World R:2" from its allegedly corrupt, PK-ridden state to the prominent "The World" of the past. Moon Tree is the greatest opposing force to Kestrel. Members are generally forbidden to PK or PKK unless they themselves are attacked, or if they are fighting in the Arena.</Word>
		<Word ID="50" Name="Steam Bike">Steam Bikes are steam-powered motorcycles used by guild leaders and those rich enough to afford one in "The World R:2". They offer a considerable boost in speed in both fields and root towns. However, Steam Bikes cannot be used in dungeons. Bikes have their own category in the Book of Thousands.</Word>
		<Word ID="51" Name="Chim Chim">Chim Chims are small, four-legged creatures found hidden in trees, giant mushrooms, and other places in the fields and dungeons of "The World R:2".</Word>
		<Word ID="52" Name="Vak Don">Vak Don is a fire spell used by the Demonic Blade in .hack//QUARANTINE.</Word>
		<Word ID="53" Name="Twin Blade">Twin Blade is a class in "The World" and "The World R:2" which wields dual blades. It is the only class "carried over" between revisions.</Word>
		<Word ID="54" Name="Gale Blade">Gale Blade is Haseo's first attack skill in .hack//G.U. Vol. 1.</Word>
		<Word ID="55" Name="Tiger Blitz">Tiger Blitz is a skill that can be learned by an Edge Punisher.</Word>
		<Word ID="56" Name="Twin Moons">Twin Moons is a skill that can be learned by an Edge Punisher.</Word>
		<Word ID="57" Name="Thorn Dance">Thorn Dance is a skill that can be learned by a Lord Partizan.</Word>
		<Word ID="58" Name="Warrior Seal">A Warrior Seal is a consumable item that temporarily lowers Physical Attack by 3 for the target.</Word>
		<Word ID="59" Name="Knight Seal">A Knight Seal is a consumable item that temporarily lowers Physical Defense by 3 for the target.</Word>
		<Word ID="60" Name="Wizard Seal">A Wizard Seal is a consumable item that temporarily lowers Magic Attack by 3 for the target.</Word>
		<Word ID="61" Name="Smoke Screen">A Smoke Screen is a consumable item that temporarily renders a party invisible to escape battle.</Word>
		<Word ID="62" Name="Raven Key">Raven Key is the guest key to enter Raven's @HOME.</Word>
		<Word ID="63" Name="Lumina Cloth">Lumina Cloth houses the Arena and the @HOME of Icolo, a guild consisting of the Arena Emperors. Having no fields or dungeons linked to it via its chaos gate, the only PKing that can occur in Lumina Cloth is in the Arena. Since it houses the Arena, Lumina Cloth is frequented by players of all levels, and is an ideal place to obtain rare items through trade.</Word>
		<Word ID="64" Name="Dol Dona">Dol Dona is the intermediate root town. Medium-sized guilds' @HOMEs are located here.</Word>
		<Word ID="65" Name="The World">"The World" is the first massively multi-player online RPG since the Pluto's Kiss incident, which nearly destroyed the global network infrastructure. Developed for the ALTIMIT OS, "The World" had a lot of media hype, resulting in over 100,000 preorders being taken in November of 2007. "The World" was sold online for download, and in the first day alone it sold 4,576,623 copies.</Word>
	</WordList>
</DataDrainConfig>
